

Iosifina Margari

Contact

josephinemrg@gmail.com



+306981066042



Syros, Greece

About me

I am a hard working designer, with passion on social media marketing. I am an excellent team worker and am able to take instructions from all levels and build up good working relationships with all colleagues. I have developed good planning & organisational skills and I am always enthusiastic to learn and undertake new challenges. I am friendly, helpful and polite and with a great sense of humor.

Certifications

Certificate of Competency in English

May 2011

Diplôme d'études en langue française DELF B1

May 2010

Microsoft Office Specialist

Mar 2009

Work Experience

Social Media Manager

TEDxUniversityoftheAegean

May 2016 - Till Now

Editorial Assistant

Frapress.gr

Jan 2017 - Apr 2017

Columnist

Frapress.gr

Oct 2016 - Jul 2017

Education

University of the Aegean

Product and Systems Design Engineering Sept 2014 - Till Now

17th Lyceum of Athens

High School Diploma

Sept 2011 - June 2014

Skills

Marketing

Social Media

Customer Service

Adobe Creative Suite

Time Management

Team Management













